var questions = [
  {
    question: 'True or False: The DOM is built into the Javascript language.',
    choices: 'True, False'.split(', '),
    answer: 'False',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following function of Array object extracts a section of an array and returns a new array?',
    choices: 'reverse(), shift(), slice(), some()'.split(', '),
    answer: 'slice()',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following function of Array object returns the last (greatest) index of an element within the array equal to the specified value, or -1 if none is found?',
    choices: 'indexOf(), join(), lastIndex(), map()'.split(', '),
    answer: 'indexOf()',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following function of String object combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?',
    choices: 'add(), merge(), concat(), append()'.split(', '),
    answer: 'concat()',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location through the specified number of characters?',
    choices: 'slice(), split(), substr(), search()'.split(', '),
    answer: 'substr()',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following function of String object returns a string representing the specified object?',
    choices: 'toLocaleUpperCase(), toUpperCase(), toString(), substring()'.split(', '),
    answer: 'toString()',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which built-in method sorts the elements of an array?',
    choices: ['changeOrder(order)', 'order()', 'sort()', 'None of the above.'],
    answer: 'sort()',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is true about variable naming conventions in JavaScript?',
    choices: ['JavaScript variable names must begin with a letter or the underscore character.', 'JavaScript variable names are case sensitive.', 'Both of the above.', 'None of the above.'],
    answer: 'Both of the above.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Commonly used data types DO Not Include:',
    choices: 'strings, booleans, alerts, numbers'.split(', '),
    answer: 'alerts',
  },
  {
    question: 'The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed with ________',
    choices: 'quotes, curly brackets, parenthesis, square brackets'.split(', '),
    answer: 'parenthesis',
  },
];
